[Music]
upon a time there were three significant
exactly p for big ones funeral things
you had to use her peninsula money and
then she died now victory was taught
with big to in slope which was the
cosigner this new burden last victory so
poor and he lost his house to do with
Hatcher ad stiglitz college savings food
then they trade I and it's bigger the
first course and a bundle microwave life
insurance should i save those things
then why do these people know what do
people need to know people are being
people are getting what's life insurance
[Music]
the concept of life insurance started
with the simple act of passing the Hat
similar to the Abu Lloyd in facility by
sharing the burden these groups were
able to share risk and do copper the
week or two be difficult accomplished
individuals
[Music]
this process is called cooperatively
sharing this always associated with
death life insurance is formally defined
as a legal agreement where an insurance
company agrees to pay some money the
cash benefit plays vision issues when
the exam covers the device life
insurance take the place of the income
you provide your family independent did
you know that people may have different
payment amounts of the new what is he
bringing the life insurance plan the
insured makes payments called renew this
posted risk will depend on a number of
factors such as age medical and health
conditions smoking habits hobbies and
education among others the higher the
posted risk the more expensive the
premium get
this process that determines your
payment beach any number of factors to
the stage medical and health conditions
moving habit obvious and allocation
among others is called underwriting let
us proceed to the main types of life
insurance the categories of life
insurance are term life and permanent
life both types provides the cash payout
of one year then permanent life combines
that with investment features so the
pulser community cash value firm life is
much cheaper and also much easier term
life covers you for a specific amount of
time which will easily between 10 to 30
years permanent live coverage of you
life as long as you pay the premium
[Music]
which do you prefer firm life or
permanent life we learned a lot about
life insurance that work is the purpose
of life insurance
[Music]
what is the importance of having a life
insurance how are you benefited one
currently production of the family to
financial security at old age unless the
Israeli found me especially here dings
estimated value for further explanation
about life insurance let's watch our
video man
[Music]
always gonna be like this myself that my
wonderful and I of training devices in
anticipation financial services for you
[Music]
what a life insurance company and well
write the way to so-called the life
insurance companies for financial
services happening where we provide our
services for will contain both social
design mint and occasionally have
affection for the future of our site
next to Oprah Josh rgc
[Music]
when I stopped exactly well this is an
international company started intended
that you can see in 27 and then we had a
functional Asia elysium 07 and this year
we're celebrating our 100th and affinity
[Music]
i usually do the first president of man
you like to search and mcdonald is
actually the Prime Minister first Prime
Minister of Canada
some night
[Music]
the mission inhibition of the companies
are well worth the mission is to be able
to professional financial services
organization in the world and to provide
strong reliable trustworthy and
forward-thinking solutions for a sign
for significant financial picture
[Music]
I'll open a light in here definitely
effective for friends events financial
services who overcame how many banks did
gampaha had angered a how many bunches
he actually had another virgin teen
Philippe's not are not to ensure about
the numbers that are we having mmm over
2,000 racial how they definitely as you
have heard about the session of the
companies would like to be the most
professional financial services
therefore I will always want to use the
best and whatever values is to gue are
pills that learn of our values is we are
valued the customers so we really focus
on customer service where their area
codes and regulations
definitely this to me to get the better
I entirely or maybe as long as you we
have what we call underwriting union and
we accept them based on the climate of
the man nervous or in general comments
will have the phone under idea how is
the magnet how do you use well any
institutions always why they might work
so basically during that you simply do
don't associate the reason oranges
company how do you manage the group of
prettier competitors in that nature well
where is the fastest-growing insurance
company in kind of exchange it means
that we have three people we have good
leadership good management all the
things marketing related how do you
recommend people they apply any less
insurance so didn't how I made this
underpinning we recommend your bucket
pail and women are not apply for
licensure definitely along if your
preparation is one preparation for the
future life insurance is not allowed of
course the demise of the red leader that
is actually the preparation preparation
for the family at the same time as I
mentioned CEO
wealth management services right
everyone I believe should beware for
their retirement with education of their
kids so so far we are faultless is to
help people learn in future we on how do
you compare this company from other life
insurance contract when you see
comparison in terms of products we have
I believe that we have the best product
we have the best people at the same time
it's more on our examples as an
insurance company and definitely
everyone that always wants to be the
number one night so we are proud to say
that right number one in terms of market
capitalization they are what are the
common inglis's of applicants regarding
to the applying relationship health
because they have what is all the
qualities of a prospect or in good
advice on good client so easy hindrances
is there are you decide the application
or learning the process of well region
says we just don't accept anyone in life
insurance industry we have as I've
mentioned to you because of evaluation
self-evaluation SMS with valuation a
financial risk about those the
hindrances what are the requirements of
the clients seem to have a life
insurance well definitely should have
money to afford the services but it's
not 3d the priority because what we
wouldn't want really is to help people
so basically you look at the bachelor to
look at all for the health of the first
thing the application
well as I've mentioned health and
physical and pieces of financial
underrated ultimately also helped that
including the occupation of individual
okay what are the car what was the
common challenges the this company three
open challenges or marketing or control
and an approach to the nine separate
individuals and then the economy white
all white house building building a new
company or immunities what are the
common problem the this company is
paying in the pen local travel criminals
and coordination to publish it again are
you after now so far we do we know doing
so well very well as the content over
her whether the what is the biggest
problem you experience or your beauty in
this country as a trainee Africa a state
council as a company I really can't so I
think of one that the company is with
people decide because the formalities we
have goes
dimension
what are the features know that it's a
shipment we want to mention active of
not enrolled children so basically the
parent well these are internal affairs
information but definitely worth the
most companies that you wanna sell some
elevation is confident what are the
services that the communication in the
future will be about being we have
suggested we just have to look into
different corners and also special
service economy kind of their conscience
economy has a sensitivity so you
probably have heard about the stock
market event one so where are you and
expenses you know be all I have learned
the supper
ok
[Music]